Legend Street,
Odoomu Area,
Iseyin,
Oyo state,
Nigeria,
08053529745,
07068833625,
odeleyeyemisi@gmail.com.

# **ODELEYE OLUYEMISI JANET**

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Certified and experienced educator with over 20 years of teaching across subjects including Agricultural Science, General Studies, and Mathematics. Registered with the Teachers Registration Council of Nigeria (TRCN), and a graduate of Mathematics Education from the National Teachers' Institute (NTI, 2022). A self-motivated small-scale business owner with strong skills in customer service, product sales, and inventory management. Known for integrating real life applications into classroom teaching and for engaging actively with students and community

#### **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

Classroom Teaching & Lesson Planning, Mathematics & Agricultural Education, Curriculum Development, Business & Sales Management, Customer Relations, Educational Mentorship, Communication & Teamwork, Financial & Inventory Management

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **TEACHER**

2005-Present.

Teaching, Civil Servant - Nigeria

## TEACHER - AGRICULTURAL SCIENCE, GENERAL SUBJECTS & MATHEMATICS

ADS Basic School Ebedi, Iseyin - Nigeria 2007 - Present

Teach Agricultural Science, General Studies, and Mathematics for basic levels. Prepare and implement lesson plans in alignment with curriculum requirements, Conduct student evaluations, class activities, and mentorship. Actively participate in school events, PTA, and extracurricular programs

#### **BUSINESS OWNER**

Jan 2000- Present.

Self-Employed - Nigeria.

Handle day-to-day operations including sales, marketing, and customer service. Manage stock, maintain financial records, and ensure product quality. Provide on-the-job training to assistants or apprentice.

### EDUCATION NATIONAL TEACHER'S INSTITUTE (NTI)

Bachelor of Education in Mathematics – Graduated 2022

#### OYO STATE COLLEGE OF EDUCATION, OYO

Nigeria Certificate in Education (NCE) - Dec 2006

#### **DOUBLE MAJOR IN AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION**

Additional coursework in General Studies and Teaching Practice

Grade: C-Merit

#### COMMUNICATION

#### SSO TRAINIG PRESENTATION

I presented a wave presentation on the topic "Improving classroom management".

# I ALSO PRERSENTED A FRENDLY AND SOCIAL PRESENTATION IN MY SCHOOL ON MICRO-TEACHING.

#### **LEADERSHIP**

# EXAMINER OF ACADEMIC ACCOUNT, NUT, ISEYIN LOCAL GOVERNMENT

#### **REFERENCES**

#### MRS. IPADEOLA A.O

Headmistress, Army Children Basic School. Barracks, Iseyin, Oyo state, Nigeria.

08109898988

# MRS. OLAWALE A.

Medical Laboratory Scientist, Hope Rising Hospital, Iseyin, Oyo state,

Nigeria.

08034894336

### MR. ODELEYE J.O

BSC Mathematic and Computer, MIC, Government Office, Ibadan, Oyo state,

Nigeria.

08058553388